©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
FEMALE RADIO ANNOUNCER 1 : This is J. T.L. Morning News .
This is Holly Chadwick .
FEMALE RADIO ANNOUNCER 2 : Thanks for joining us .
We have a great show in store for you this morning .
MALE RADIO ANNOUNCER : Well , it 's a great morning to be in the studio .
BRITISH NEWSMAN 1 : Authorities have confirmed an avian flu outbreak .
WEATHERMAN : Forecast , cloudy skies ...
NEWSMAN 2 : Good morning .
Reporting from Brighton .
MALE EPIDEMIOLOGIST : This will be a different scenario
if the virus changes in a way that allows transmission between humans .
- So , let 's get started . -
FEMALE REPORTER 1 : Yet again today ,
another group of dolphins became stranded .
CO2 emissions have dramatically increased in ...
TV ANCHORMAN : Are there any real threats that you know of ?
Not at all .
SOUTH AFRICAN NEWSWOMAN : Environmentalists are trying
to determine the cause of death .
FEMALE REPORTER 2 : At alert level six ,
W.H.O. guidelines for governments ...
Your socks are so cute ! I like them .
Police say they 've seen similar cases recently
of people behaving strangely .
TV ANCHORWOMAN : The U.N. health agency is not likely
to recommend official travel restrictions .
OLDER BRITISH MAN : It 's a little bit unsettling .
MICHIO KAKU : They 're not physicists .
They 're not engineers .
They think it 's just gonna go away .
They live in a fantasy parallel universe .
FEMALE CALLER : Right on top of the man , beating him .
The man is bleeding .
BRITISH NEWSMAN : Twenty-one confirmed cases .
All the talk about a doomsday is a big hoax .
MALE REPORTER : The subject growled at him
and continued to maul the victim .
NEWSWOMAN : The best estimate is about 15,000 in the U. K.
EPIDEMIOLOGIST : We don 't know if this is spreading .
BRITISH NEWSMAN : Rhythms of change ...
EPIDEMIOLOGIST : So far there 's no manifestation .
MAN 1 : Monitors have arrived , even carrying them ...
MAN 2 : With that much public at risk , we cannot ...
MAN 3 : They 're trying to move us on , trying to tell the journalists to get out .
CONNIE : Wake up !
- Oh , creatures in our bed ... -
- No sleeping ! -
Oh , you 're getting very big .
- What do you want to eat ?
- GIRLS : Pancakes !
We got a lot more sunshine today .
You have to only say one word .
GERRY : Hey , by the way , what do you want for your birthday ?
say a puppy -
A PUPPY -
GERRY : You mean a stuffed animal puppy ?
Because that we can do .
Scusi .
KARIN : Good morning .
That looks yummy .
RACHEL : She gets the bigger one ?
CONNIE : Yeah , sorry .
KARIN : She 's tiny .
Did you pack your , um , inhaler ?
Bathroom sink .
- In a minute ? - Scootch ! Go .
MALE REPORTER : The government has declared martial law .
Daddy , what 's martial law ?
Uh ...
Martial law is like house rules , but for everybody .
Were you ever in places like that with your old job ?
GERRY : Mmm-hmm .
But I quit my old job so I could be with you .
Do you miss it ?
GERRY : No , I like my new job .
All you do is make pancakes in the morning !
Yeah , but I 'm really good at it .
-  Look who I found ! - Oh !
STUFFED ANIMAL : Here comes the number 12 train !
GERRY : It 's not Subway Sam , is it ?
You want more pancakes ?
Good .
Go , go , go . Come on , scootch !
CONNIE : At least ...
KARIN : Move it on out .
Hey ! Plates in the sink !
CONNIE : Later !
KARIN : Do that when we get back !
Uh ... Does it live in the jungle ?
Oooh .
No .
Do you eat it on Sundays ?
Does it live on the Great Plains of Africa ?
- Yeah . - Oh , well , I guess , yeah .
Do people keep it in pens all its life and harvest it for meat ?
That 's really gross !
RACHEL : Gross !
Dad !
Is it an animal you 'd have for a pet ?
- Yes . - Is it a cat ?
- RACHEL : Yes . - Ha ha ha .
Okay , now we have another one .
Do another one .
-  - You totally got one !
Why are there so many ?
It 's like , three in the last five minutes .
-  - What is going on ?
-  -
RADIO ANCHORMAN : The World Health Organization has been
tracking the recent outbreak of rabies
that began in Taiwan and has now been reported in over 12 countries .
Responding to allegations he hasn 't done enough to prevent the spread ...
Can we try BBC ?
You 're not British anymore , baby .
You lost your accent a long time ago .
Except after two bottles of wine .
Am I British ?
Yeah , your grandma is .
- Hey ! - Yo !
He 's just gonna keep going , Daddy ?
Hold on , guys .
RACHEL : Daddy , be careful on the road .
GERRY : It 's okay , baby .
ANCHORMAN : Can be transmitted between species
commonly from a bite from an infected animal .
Our best recommendation is to stay away from densely populated areas .
Hey , yo ! You all right ?
Yeah , I 'm okay . Thanks .
- You need anything ?
- No . You know what 's going on ?
No , man , I don 't know anything .
It 's crazy .
- -
Gerry ?
Get back in your car right now !
Remain with your ve ...
- -
What are we doing ?
GERRY : That 's our way out of here .
I want my blanket !
Baby , it 's packed right now .
Snuggle with Subway Sam , okay ?
My blanket !
Rach ?
Rachel , baby , you 've got to get back in your seat .
Baby , we need you in your seat .
GERRY : Put your belt on !
KARIN : Rachel , right now !
- Gerry ? - Rach , get your belt back on !
- You okay ? - GERRY : You okay ?
- Rachel , sweetheart ?
- Rachel , you hurt ?
- KARIN : Connie ?
- Are you okay ? It 's okay .
We should get out .
Everybody out of the car .
GERRY : We 've got to get out of the city .
Her door won 't open !
Rachel , go out that side .
Okay , you have to climb over , honey .
OFFICER : Out of the way !
Move it !
Come on , honey .
Come on .
Sweetheart , are you okay ?
Let 's go .
Let 's get off the street .
What is that , Gerry ?
What is that ?
I don 't know !
Get to the RV .
Subway Sam !
Here comes the number 12 train ! One .
Two .
- What 's happening ?
- SUBWAY SAM : Three .
Four .
- - Five .
Six .
Seven .
- - Eight .
Nine .
Ten .
Eleven .
Twelve .
Train 's in the station !
Gerry !
- KARIN : Watch out ! -
POLICEMAN : We 're pulling back on Fifth Street !
COMMAND OFFICER : Containment is a fail .
- KARIN : Try to relax . -
Give yourself air .
In and out .
- Come on , baby , try to relax . -
Gerry ? We left my purse in the car .
Where 's her spare ?
I 'm gonna go check your backpack , all right ?
Do you want to be with her ?
GERRY : Rach , you 'll be all right .
You 're gonna be all right .
Hey , hey , you breathe through your nose .
Rach , Rach , look at me . Look at me .
You 're gonna be all right .
You 've done this a hundred times .
Look at me . Look at me .
Breathe in through your nose , out through your mouth .
Okay , we 're gonna go to a pharmacy .
We got to move .
Okay .
-  - GERRY : Good . Good . Look .
Look at me , look at me .
Rach , breathe through your nose .
KARIN : No , no , no , no ...
You 're gonna be all right .
- Look at me .
- Daddy , what are those things ?
Honey , find us some water .
Okay ? Something to drink .
It 's Thierry .
Where are you ?
THIERRY : Airborne . Lower East Side to Turtle Bay .
It 's all gone . We barely made it out .
Tell him to go south .
No , no , we need visual confirmation .
-  - No , no , no , no , no , no , no .
What is this ?
We don 't know . How close were you ?
Face to face .
Good , honey , good .
Daddy .
Connie , give me that .
Give me that .
Oh , thank you , honey .
THIERRY : Where are you ?
GERRY : 95 , heading north .
-  - Okay . Okay .
THIERRY : All right .
We 'll try to get a helicopter to you .
I 'll call you back with an extraction point .
Can you hold out for another hour ?
Do we have a choice ?
This is not for old time 's sake , my friend .
I 'll need you .
I need you back .
Don 't forget about us .
What do you mean , we 've lost Boston ?
All right . Good luck , Gerry .
Okay .
Good , honey . Keep it going .
It 's gonna be all right .
Come here . Stay close .
Super close .
Take my hand .
Get her medicine , I 'll get us something to eat .
I 'll meet you back here .
Stay close , honey .
What do you need ?
Albuterol .
They outgrow the asthma supposedly .
And this shit , too .
It 's magic for my kid .
GERRY : Thank you .
CONNIE : Daddy !
GERRY : Connie ?
Daddy !
- Connie ? - CONNIE : Daddy !
- Where 's Mommy ?
- KARIN : Gerry !
Gerry !
Karin ?
- Karin ? - KARIN : Gerry ! Gerry !
Get off of me !
Get off of me ! That 's all I have .
- Gerry ! - Hey !
- Hey ! - Gerry .
OFFICER :  Multiple 11-99s at Washington Park .
Please , send units .
We 're falling back on Reed Street .
FEMALE DISPATCH : Two Robert 12 , units need backup .
Mobile ops is down .
Please respond .
Two Robert 12 , are you there ? Copy .
- GERRY : Girls ! - Responders , Code 3 , Code 3 .
KARIN : Rachel , quick , come on .
No .
No !
We got to get out of here .
We got to get off the street .
Gerry .
Apartments ?
Hey . Yeah .
- Gerry ? - We 're in Newark .
We 're stranded .
Apartment buildings , 23rd .
If we can get to the roof , can you get someone to us ?
- Not tonight . - When ?
The earliest would be sunrise .
Sunrise .
Tell him I got flares .
GERRY : We 'll be on the roof with flares .
Listen , Gerry , I will move mountains to get you out here .
- - Come here , baby .
Go ! Go ! Go !
KARIN : Baby , in here !
GERRY : Come on . Quick !
Gerry !
Inside , girls !
By the stairs . Inside , inside !
GERRY : Wait !
Wait .
KARIN : Up , up .
It 's okay , baby .
- -
Run ! Run ! Go , Rachel !
KARIN : Go !
GERRY : Go !
Keep running , baby .
KARIN : It 's all right .
GERRY : To the top .
GO ! Go !
Go !
Run !
Go ! Go ! Go ! Go !
I need a new flare !
This asshole 's about to get through !
KARIN : Where 's Connie ? Connie ?
GERRY : Connie ? KARIN : Connie !
CONNIE : Let me in !
KARIN : Connie !
- Baby ? - It 's not her . It 's not her .
- Let me in ! - Connie !
Let me in !
In , in , in ! In !
Thank you so much .
- I 'm Tomas . - GERRY : Hey , Tomas .
TOMAS : My mom 's cooking everything before it starts to stink .
GERRY : That 's smart .
You guys all right ?
It 's all right .
It 's okay .
Are you guys hungry ' ?
Yes , thank you .
TOMAS : Here you go .
Thank you .
- Thank you . -
KARIN : You want some juice ?
ROBOTIC MALE VOICE : The following message
is transmitted at the request of the New Jersey State Police Department .
Authorities recommend that the following actions
should be taken by all the members of the public .
Stay indoors if at all possible .
Have enough food and water supplies for sheltering
for one to two weeks .
The following message is transmitted at the request
of the New Jersey State Police Department .
An unidentified virus strain is rapidly
spreading across the state of New Jersey .
- -
She was crying .
GERRY : Hmm .
Thanks , Tommy .
I used to work in dangerous places
and people who moved survived , and those who didn 't ...
Movement is life .
You have a better chance if you come with us .
You need anything else before you leave ?
GERRY : Okay . Come on . Come on .
We should have left with them .
There is nowhere to go .
What 's going to happen when the food is gone ?
- -
Okay , come on .
I 'm scared .
Connie , there 's a helicopter waiting for us on the roof .
Keep your eyes on Mommy and Daddy , okay ?
Be ninja quiet .
Just a walk in the park .
How do we know they 're coming ?
They 're coming .
Ready ?
- GERRY : Okay , come on , guys . -
- -
Come on ! Come on !
KARIN : UP , UP , UP -
GERRY : Come on , baby .
Go , go , go !
Come on , baby !
KARIN : Go , go !
Go , girls ! Gerry !
Come on . Gerry !
Girls , get back !
Watch out !
- Go ! - Go , go , go !
Come on , faster , girls !
PILOT : Lieutenant , I 've got no contact .
I say again , no contact .
-  - GERRY : Let 's go , let 's go !
Karin !
- Karin ! - Yeah .
Go through the door !
Gerry ?
PILOT : There they are !
Ace , we have positive contact .
That 's our target !
Get us down !
Daddy !
- Daddy ! - Baby , get back .
CONNIE : Daddy !
Gerry ?
- Gerry , what ? - Stay back !
Baby ! No !
One thousand seven .
One thousand eight .
CONNIE : Daddy , get off the edge !
- KARIN : Gerry , please ?
- One thousand ten .
One thousand eleven .
I got it in my mouth .
You 're okay . You 're okay .
-  - Go ! Go !
Come on . Come on .
SOLDIER : Let 's go !
Let 's go !
Come on , let 's go !
We got to go !
KARIN : You got her ?
Let 's go , let 's go , let 's go !
CONTROLLER : Traffic en route , altitude 5-7 thousand .
Heading 250 .
Turn right , heading 075 , once clear .
Remain below 4,000 .
Clear to land , heading 040 , wind 060 at five .
Follow L.S.O. directions .
Prep for immediate dust off .
THIERRY : Gerry .
GERRY : Thank you .
THIERRY : Good to see you , my friend .
CONTROLLER : Tango five , this is Argus command .
Cleared for take-off .
PILOT : Tango five . Wilco .
THIERRY : Karin , to the right .
This is good , right ?
GERRY : Bunk beds !
Your bunk beds are number two , three and six .
Please make yourself at home .
You want to get up here ?
There you go , sweetheart .
KARIN : That 's good .
THIERRY : We 're not dropping anchor again .
You 're safe .
It 's not me I 'm worried about .
They 're safe .
KARIN : Baby .
It 's bigger than our old apartment on 72nd .
Need anything , Karin ?
Water .
I 'll organize .
Is this worldwide ?
Is anyone doing better than we are ?
Baby . Go talk somewhere else .
Okay .
The President is dead .
Four of six Joint Chiefs . V.P. missing .
Reports of gun battles in the streets of the capital .
Your parties are panicking .
The bigger cities are the worst off .
The airlines were the perfect delivery system .
Carnival cruise vessel Dream has been given permission to join .
Twenty seven knots south and closing .
How soon are they showing symptoms after contact ?
TECHNICIAN 1 : The provisional government currently considers
northern Minnesota to be a potential safe zone .
TECHNICIAN 2 : Have you recorded any instance where a person
was bitten but not infected ?
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
How the hell do I know if Russia 's fallen ?
Sir , I cannot action that order .
Colonel , I 'm sorry , but we cannot facilitate
an evacuation for you or your men .
Sir , there is nowhere to evacuate you to .
Malnutrition . Dirty water .
No gas for the winter or transportation .
No bullets to fight .
And it has spread to all corners of the globe .
MICHAEL : The question that we have got to address
is what the hell is it ?
About 5 % of the population aren 't affected immediately .
It is viral .
It has to be viral .
There is no plausible alternative .
And like any virus , once we find its origin , we can develop a vaccine .
We find it , contain it ...
That 's Dr. Fassbach .
Virologist from Harvard .
The analogy I keep coming back to
is Spanish Flu .
Spanish Flu ?
It didn 't exist in 1918 , but by 1920 ,
it killed 3 % of the world .
He 's our best bet at figuring out what this thing is .
You all read the same email I did ,
- and it said " zombies . " -
Are you completely out of your mind ?
So , the earliest mention of the word " zombie "
was in a memo from Camp Humphreys in South Korea .
We haven 't had contact with them since .
But this could lead us to the origin .
If we knew where this thing started ,
then we 'd have a chance of developing a vaccine to stop it .
So we send in Dr. Fassbach there to look for the source .
He 's just a kid .
You 're right .
SERGEANT : Attention on deck !
At ease !
Mr. Under-Secretary .
The Under-Secretary here says you were
his best investigator when you were at the U.N.
I want to send you in . With a team .
Help Dr. Fassbach find whatever it is he needs .
You brought ...
I wanted for the circumstances to speak for themselves .
No .
Captain , I 'm not your guy .
You were on the ground during the Liberian Civil War .
Investigated Chechen war crimes .
Sri Lanka in ' 07 .
Places you and I both know Dr. Fassbach wouldn 't last a night in .
Gerry , a handful of SEALS will go with you as security force .
No .
My guys will get you in , you assist the doctor ,
pursue any leads , my guys will get you out .
We do the heavy lifting .
I can 't help you . I can 't leave my family .
Take a look around here , Mr. Lane .
Each and every one of these people are here because they serve a purpose .
There 's no room here for non-essential personnel .
There 's a long line of people
waiting for one of those bunks .
You want to help your family ,
let 's figure out how we stop this .
It 's your choice , Mr. Lane .
Simple .
KARIN : You don 't work for them anymore .
- Karin ... - You might not remember
what this job did to you , but I do .
So do not ask me to say yes to this .
I have to go .
They 're going to kick us off the ship .
What ?
If I go , you , the girls , Tommy , have a place to stay .
If I don 't , we 're back in Philly tonight .
What about Thierry ?
Can 't he do anything ?
Men like Thierry aren 't in charge of anything anymore .
You keep this with you .
I 'll call in once a day .
As long as I make that call , everything 's gonna be okay .
I 'm coming back .
Okay ? We 're going to make the best of it .
As we do .
Like we do .
Okay , baby doll , Daddy 's got to go to work .
I 'm not a baby .
Okay .
Tall , beautiful , tiny adult .
I 'll be back soon .
Yeah ?
All right , tough guy ...
Take care of the ladies for me ?
Yeah .
Deal .
You 're awesome .
Daddy 's coming back .
This way , sir .
GERRY : Look .
We don 't know what we 're walking into .
So we do what they say . Okay .
If they move , we move .
If they stop , we stop .
If things were to get crazy ,
just focus on their boots ,
focus on their voices , and we 'll be all right .
FASSBACH : Mmm-hmm .
These guys are hammers .
And to hammers , everything looks like nails .
I heard that .
You were meant to .
So , you see something that 's important ,
you call it out and we 'll make it happen .
Okay .
You think we 're gonna find anything ?
Yeah .
Yeah , we 're gonna find something .
Mother Nature is a serial killer .
No one 's better .
More creative .
But like all serial killers ,
she can 't help the urge to want to get caught .
What good are all those brilliant crimes
if no one takes the credit ?
So she leaves crumbs .
Now , the hard part , why you spend a decade in school ,
is seeing the crumbs for the clues they are .
Sometimes the thing you thought
was the most brutal aspect of the virus ,
turns out to be the chink in its armour .
And she loves disguising her weaknesses as strengths .
She 's a bitch .
NAVY TECHNICIAN : Attention .
D.C. has gone dark . I repeat ,
D.C. has gone dark .
The Capitol evacuation has been suspended .
All available resources should be directed to Naval Station Norfolk .
WARRANT OFFICER : All non-essential personnel
given F-6 status and in groups A through E
need to report to the flight deck for relocation .
Groups A and B relocating to Orlando
should be on the stern clear of the landing zone .
I say again , all non-essential personnel given F-6 status
need to report to the flight deck .
Choppers are inbound for immediate relocation .
Mommy , is this dinner ?
Yes , sweetheart .
Water here tastes funny .
It 's jet fuel , young lady .
He 's joking .
I wish . Desal has trouble filtering it out .
Probably because there 's too many people on this ship .
PILOT : Everybody wake up .
We 're on approach to Camp Humphreys .
Most of the base is dark , and no one is manning the tower .
We 're running on fumes , so there 's really no choice ,
I 've got to put us down .
So buckle up .
GERRY : Hold up .
Keep your finger off the trigger .
Okay .
-
Fassbach ! Wait !
GERRY : Damn it .
SEAL COMMANDER : Move back !
SPEKE : Friendly ! Friendly !
Keep it down . Keep it down .
What is this ?
What happened to him ?
He slipped . He 's dead .
Come on !
Come on ! Let 's go !
Let 's go !
SPEKE : Okay , I 'm good !
- Who was it ? Who fell ?
- LINCOLN : Skilken .
- Hold ! Clear . - Hold .
SPEKE : I want an ammo count , then you reload your mags !
RANGER : Yes , sir !
My boy who just died out there was 23 .
He was 23 .
You want to tell me why ?
Because the guy who just shot himself , he 's a doctor , a virologist .
What are you talking about ?
GERRY : He was supposed to be our best hope .
Well , he 's not our best hope anymore .
Hey . That guy volunteered to come here .
He didn 't have to , you know .
None of them did .
We 're still trying to figure out what the hell this thing is .
Well , shit happens .
The doctor would have strongly agreed with you .
How do we go about refuelling ?
When I say so . And very carefully .
The noise , are they drawn to it ?
Yeah . Sound draws them .
Body shots only seem to slow them down .
Head shots do the trick , but just to be safe
we tend to burn them when we can .
- You fought any Zeke yet ? - GERRY : Yeah .
- SPEKE : Where ? - Philly . Newark .
Bad ?
- What about Houston ? - St. Louis ?
- Baltimore ? - MALE RANGER : Atlanta ?
FEMALE RANGER : Detroit ?
Guys , I 'll be honest with you ,
I don 't know of any place back home that 's doing very well .
All right ...
If the other guy was a virologist , what do you do ?
There was a memo sent from this installation 11 days ago .
It had the word " zombie " in it .
Do you know anything about it ?
Yeah .
It was an email , not a memo .
Pretty obvious nobody back home bothered to read it .
Now , there 's 15 , 16 guys in this room .
Most of them guards . But all of them were bitten
trying to get this man handcuffed to the cot .
Now , our colonel said he was the first one .
This colonel , is he around ?
Oh , yeah . He 's right here .
The guy who 's shackled , do you know
who bit him , what bit him ?
SPEKE : He was the base doctor .
He 'd just returned from the field .
He 'd been sent out to verify the death of a soldier
who had just gone AWOL the week before .
Some villagers had found this guy
foaming at the mouth , oozing some kind of black tar .
Then he tried to bite one of them .
They shot him , tied him up , threw him in a barn .
- -
That 's all we know , except the doctor
comes back here and begins attacking his patients .
GERRY : This soldier , do you know where he came from ?
No .
GERRY : Anyone he might have come in contact with ?
There 's got to be records .
SPEKE : You are welcome to take a look if you want .
GERRY : Then the origin could have come from anywhere .
It 's a shame you had to fly
all the way out here to figure that out .
How did you all escape this ?
The expenditure of ammunition .
Is that how you tweaked your leg ?
No , shit 's been bugging me a while .
This prick stands right in the mix ,
while seven or eight of them
turn Zeke all at the same time .
But they got no time for Ol ' Dirty Bastard here .
Biting everything like fat kids love Twix .
Got no time for his lucky ass .
Ain 't it obvious I 'm charmed ?
The ones I saw bitten turned in 12 seconds .
Same here ?
Five or 10 minutes .
Yeah , Davidson went and he turned in 10 minutes .
" Stevie ?
" Captain Spekes ! Oh , my God !
My God !
My God ! Are they eating me ? "
Who 's that ?
Waste no time on that freak .
SPEKE : He 's C.I.A.
Got caught selling guns to North Korea .
Davidson ,
he turned in 10 minutes .
That doesn 't sound viral to me at all , sports fans !
You 're with the C.I.A. ?
But they 're not with me .
And who are you ?
U.N.
Oh , my God !
Captain , put on the World Music !
The day
is saved !
Why 'd you sell guns to the North ?
Why not ?
GERRY : Are they surviving this ?
Indeed they are .
Using your guns .
Guns are half-measures .
How then ?
All right .
They took away
the Zekes ' exponential power .
They pulled the teeth of all 23 million
in less than 24 hours .
The greatest feat of social engineering in history .
It 's brilliant .
No teeth ,
no bite .
No great spread .
Bullshit .
BURT : More books , fewer receptions , Boutros Boutros .
Now , why do you have to burn them
to ashes to get them to finally stop ?
Why do they move like a plague ?
Why is Israel winning ?
How is Israel winning ?
They sealed off their entire country
days before the undead attacked man .
First to know ,
first to act .
GERRY : People have been building walls there for two millennia .
Mmm . Right . Yeah , but ,
finish all those
thousands of years of work a week ago ?
Impeccable timing is all .
You want answers ?
Jurgen Warmbrunn .
That 's the man in Jerusalem you want to see .
You ever seen anything like that ?
Hell , no .
We 're going to Jerusalem .
I 'm your co-pilot .
Oh , hang on .
Hang on . Hang on a minute .
- Hello ? -
Gerry ?
- Honey ? - Gerry , can you hear me ?
Karin ?
Hello ?
- God damn it ! -
SPEKE : Give me your hand .
No way . No .
My mother . Dallas .
Probably pacing a hole in the floor right now if she 's still there .
Better chance of you seeing her before me , that 's all .
It 's a big plane . We got a lot of room .
Better the devil you know than the one you don 't .
You 'll be all right .
Just pedal your ass off .
Make sure Maverick here keeps the nose of that plane
pointed towards the sun .
Just remember , don 't lock the bowser 's fuel line to the inlet .
Tell me 10 more times .
- You good ?
- SEAL COMMANDER : Right here .
All right . Don 't rush .
We 've got one chance to fuel their plane , so let 's do it right .
If you ain 't a crack shot , don 't aim for the head ,
just get Zeke on the ground .
Remember , " Spine 's divine , those knees they work just fine ! "
Let 's go , lights out !
ALPHA TEAM LEADER : Alpha in position .
BRAVO TEAM LEADER : Bravo moving out .
SPEKE : Remember , these things are drawn to sound .
So I need you close to target before I bring you the truck .
Now there 's only one way we 're getting you on that plane ,
and that 's quietly .
-  - Shit !
SEAL COMMANDER : God damn it !
Shut that thing off !
- -
ELLIS : Looks like we just woke the dead .
SPEKE : Out of respect for others ,
please turn off all pagers and cell phones .
- -
We got to move .
We 've got to get out of here , let 's move !
Go , go , go !
SPEKE : Whoo !
I 'm gonna clear a path through Zeke !
You pedal like hell !
Come on , boys , I need head shots !
Tap ' em out !
I want to see some Zeke on the ground !
SPEKE : You 're kidding me .
I 'm a God damn Zeke .
I got you , Captain .
Just say the word .
SPEKE : It 's all right , boys .
I got this one .
God damn it .
PILOT : We got enough !
We need to detach the fuel line !
Israel better pay off .
All right , I have instrument , but only on single prop .
You 'll have to talk me through it .
Okay , we 're clear .
Okay . Give me all the lights .
Switch on the anti-icing .
- Where ? - The red knob .
Got it , got it .
Set up our heading 020 for departure .
We got to move !
Set flaps 15 degrees .
Flaps 15 .
All right , we are all set .
Let 's get out of here !
GERRY : Make it steep .
- Gerry ? - Hi , baby .
Hi . Hi .
KARIN : I tried to call you .
I know , I was ...
It was bad timing , I was running around .
Are you okay ?
Yeah , everything 's okay . I 'm okay .
That 's the spirit .
Yeah .
Listen ,
Korea didn 't work out .
Now it looks like we 're gonna have to go to Israel .
Try to get some rest on the flight .
How are the kids ?
Um ...
I think ...
They 're really ... They 're good .
I got Connie right here .
Baby ?
TRAFFIC CONTROLLER : Attention , unidentified aircraft .
You are in a restricted airspace and not clear for landing .
Jerusalem tower , Reach 394 .
Pan , pan , pan .
Request immediate landing .
Contact Mossad , office of Jurgen Warmbrunn .
Special Envoy , United Nations .
Stay with the plane .
Be ready to bug out .
I 'll be back before dark .
JURGEN : The problem with most people is that
they don 't believe something can happen
until it already has .
It 's not stupidity or weakness .
It 's just human nature .
How did you know ?
Gerald Lane .
Wrote a self-defeating Jeremiad
about his employer , the U.N. , back in 2010 .
Caused a few ripples .
Sidelined your career .
Thought you 'd have parlayed those ripples into a self-righteous book .
No nose for profit .
How did Israel know ?
We intercepted a communique from an Indian general
saying they were fighting the Rakshasha .
Translation , zombies .
Technically undead .
Jurgen Warmbrunn .
High-ranking official in the Mossad .
Described as sober , efficient , not terribly imaginative .
And yet you build a wall because you read a communique
that mentions the word " zombie " ?
Well , when put like that , I 'd be sceptical as well .
In the ' 30s , Jews refused to believe
they could be sent to concentration camps .
In ' 72 , we refused to fathom we 'd be massacred in the Olympics .
In the month before October 1973 , we saw Arab troop movements ,
and we unanimously agreed they didn 't pose a threat .
Well , a month later , the Arab attack almost drove us into the sea .
So we decided to make a change .
A change ?
The Tenth Man .
If nine of us look at the same information
and arrive at the exact same conclusion ,
it 's the duty of the tenth man to disagree .
No matter how improbable it may seem ,
the tenth man has to start digging
on the assumption that the other nine are wrong .
And you were that tenth man .
Precisely .
Since everyone assumed that this talk of zombies was cover for something else ,
I began my investigation on the assumption
that when they said " zombies , " they meant zombies .
Was patient zero from India ?
That 's the problem .
There 's so many potential sources in play
that no one knows where it began .
The organ trade in Germany .
Strange examples of violent behaviour across the Asian peninsulas .
Meanwhile , the zombie plague keeps spreading , and we do what we can .
These are the Jerusalem Salvation Gates .
Two of 10 portals
through the security perimeter into fortified Israel .
You 're letting people in .
Every human being we save is one less zombie to fight .
It 's okay .
If I could get into India , where would I start ?
Who would I speak with ?
India 's a black hole .
Forget about patient zero .
I can 't do that .
It 's too late for me to build a wall .
I 'm running out of time .
I need specifics .
I need answers ...
I don 't have answers .
All you can do is find a way to hide .
Get troops down there .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
It 's too loud ! It 's too loud !
They 're coming over the top !
- Shit ! -
Command , we have a breach at Salvation Gate .
They 're coming over the wall !
Get him to Jaffa Gate .
She 'll get you out of here , she 'll get you to your plane !
Stay low !
Wrong way ! Wrong way !
Go to landing point B.
Roger , we are inbound to landing point B.
Hawk 5 , almost there .
E.T.A. one minute .
DISPATCHER : Hawk 5 .
Hawk 5 , you 're patched in . Over .
This is Hawk 5 . Listen carefully .
The city is breached , and they 're heading towards the airport .
- GERRY : One thousand one . -
One thousand two .
One thousand three .
One thousand four .
- - One thousand five .
One thousand six .
One thousand seven .
One thousand eight .
We got to move .
You 'll be all right .
You 're not gonna turn .
You 're not gonna turn !
We got to move .
-  - We got to move !
5 going down .
DISPATCHER : Chopper 5 is down .
I say again , chopper 5 is down .
L.Z. is overrun .
Tower , Reach 394 .
Requesting immediate departure .
MALE DISPATCHER : Tower to 394 .
Proceed to runway four .
Good luck out there .
No !
There ! That one !
Stop . Stop .
GO ! Go !
Get them out of here !
STEWARD : Stay calm , please .
Stay calm .
Come on . Go , go , go .
What 's your destination ?
I don 't know . We were headed here , but I don 't know .
I 'm Gerry , by the way .
Segen .
GERRY : Segen .
First or last ?
Just Segen .
So , what we 're doing ,
we 've got to change this bandage and we 're gonna clean it .
Okay ?
You okay ? Okay ?
Okay .
Come on , gut up . Gut up .
Here we go .
We 're almost there .
Okay . Big breaths .
Let 's get this over fast . Big breaths .
Here we go .
Come on .
Good .
Last step . Last step .
Big breath .
Good job . There it is .
Okay . Mmm-hmm .
Okay . Okay , I think you 've earned this .
Very good . Okay .
You a doctor ?
No .
I 've had some training in the field .
SEGEN : How did you know ?
Cutting it off ...
How did you know it would work ?
I didn 't .
Now I 'm just a liability .
SPEKE : This prick
stands right in the mix ,
while seven or eight of them
turn Zeke all at the same time .
GERRY : Is that how you tweaked your leg ?
No , shit 's been bugging me a while .
SPEKE : Got no time for his lucky ass .
FASSBACH : Now , the hard part is seeing the crumbs
for the clues they are .
And sometimes the thing you thought
was the most brutal aspect of the virus
turns out to be the chink in its armour .
JURGEN : I don 't have answers .
All you can do is find a way to hide .
Gerry ?
Are you okay ?
Where are you , baby ?
What 's happening ?
I love you . I 'm sorry .
But you 've got to get Thierry now .
I 'll find him .
Thierry ! Thierry .
Excuse me . Karin .
KARIN : Gerry needs you .
I love you .
Gerry ? Where are you ?
On the last flight out .
Listen , my phone is dying and I need some quick Intel .
You got to locate the closest medical research facility .
A C.D.C. , a W.H.O. , something that makes vaccines .
And the closest airport to it .
I don 't understand .
No time to explain .
Just make it happen , man .
Okay , okay .
But , Gerry , I still don 't know where you are .
Well , go and find out what he needs .
You 're gonna want to take this .
Take it .
Your battery is dead .
We made contact with Cardiff Airport , Wales .
Your people directed us .
There is W.H.O. research facility nearby ,
but they are not sure it 's still operational .
This is location .
Can we make it ?
PILOT : Ladies and gentlemen , this is your Captain .
I 'm glad to report that we are on our final approach
to Cardiff Airport in Wales .
All European airports are under lockdown .
But we have been given priority status and cleared for landing .
We will be allowed to disembark .
We are very , very lucky .
Hey . Who do you belong to ?
What 's there ?
- - What is it ?
You ... Bags .
We need trolley and bags .
Mayday , mayday , mayday !
Bravo 160 heavy .
Emergency descent !
Prepare for impact .
Got to move .
Come on , come on .
Give me something good .
TECHNICIAN : Sir , Cardiff Airport lost contact with the plane .
Lane is M.I.A. I 'm sorry , sir .
WARRANT OFFICER : Chopper inbound for immediate relocation .
I say again .
All non-essential personnel given F-6 status
need to report for immediate relocation .
Ma 'am ?
Thierry would like a word with you .
Captain , it 's only been 48 hours .
He 's a resourceful man .
There 's every chance he could have survived .
Sir , I gave him my word we would look after his family .
Yes , sir . I understand .
SOLDIER : Okay .
Let 's go . We 're good .
CONNIE : Daddy !
Daddy !
BRIT : You 're a tough bastard .
And a lucky one .
Who are you ?
I came here with a ... With a woman .
Is she still ...
BRIT : Who are you ?
Why have you come here ?
Why do you keep looking at him ?
'Cause he 's the one in charge .
You know what this place is ?
Of course I do .
That 's why I 'm here .
BRIT : Then you understand how this must look to us .
JAVIER : This
is important to you ?
- How long have I been out ?
- BRIT : Three days .
Give me the phone .
Just give me the phone .
Give me the God damn phone !
Give me the phone !
As soon as you answer my question .
Call it .
Call the number , they 'll tell you who I am .
THIERRY : Gerry ?
- Yeah , I 'm here .
I 'm here . - My God .
We thought you were dead .
Gerry , where are you ?
Thierry , I 'm with a couple of nervous gentlemen .
They need some bona fides before I can speak with you .
Of course .
This is Thierry Umutoni .
Deputy Secretary-General .
United Nations .
To whom am I speaking ?
Where 's Karin ?
Thierry , why didn 't Karin answer ?
I 'm sorry , Gerry .
I did what I could .
GERRY : What does that mean ?
You 've got to calm down .
No , stop ! Stop .
You 're going to hurt yourself .
You 're okay .
His family has been sent to a refugee camp in Nova Scotia .
I 'm sure they 'll be safe .
Are you ?
Thierry told you who I am and what I used to do , right ?
Yeah .
Then trust me when I tell you they 're not safe .
I understand how you feel .
- Do you ? Yes ? - Yes .
Do you have a family ?
- No . - No .
Then you couldn 't possibly understand , could you ?
I lost my son and wife in Rome .
Rather , I lost my son to
something that had once been my wife .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
We have all lost someone , Mr. Lane .
In your case , there is hope at least .
I 'm sorry .
Now ,
why did you come here ?
What do you need from us ?
Your worst disease .
DR. KELLY : He wants a what ?
Deadly pathogen .
With a high mortality rate .
- But curable . - Okay , well ...
You 'd want a bacteria rather than a virus ,
I would think . Typhus ?
Meningitis . Scarlet Fever .
DR. KELLY : Rocky Mountain Fever .
Anyway , excuse me , what 's this for ?
Mr. Lane believes we can use such a disease against the undead .
I would give you points for originality , Mr. Lane ,
if we hadn 't already tried that , first thing .
One of the many things a virus or bacteria needs to thrive is a live host .
A functioning circulatory system .
I 'm afraid it boils down to one simple fact ...
You can 't make a dead person sick .
It 's not for them .
It 's for us .
I believe these things have a weakness .
And that weakness is weakness .
- Our weakness . -
I have witnessed them literally bypass people .
Walk right around them like a river around a rock . Why ?
I think , because those people were sick .
I think they were terminal .
And these things could sense it .
I think they 're spreading a pathogen ,
and they need a healthy host .
But even if you 're right , I mean , infecting the populace
with a lethal illness is not exactly a cure .
It 's not a cure .
It 's camouflage .
There 's a natural precedent .
Hungry predators will avoid diseased bodies .
Equipped with the right pathogen , our troops
would be essentially invisible to the enemy .
You understand the only way to prove this theory of yours is
for some idiot to infect themselves
with a lethal pathogen and then ...
... meet with her , face to face .
Yes .
Do we have what we need to try it ?
DR. KELLY : We have all he could want .
Typhus , H1N1 , SARS .
The problem is ,
they 're all stored in B-Wing .
What 's the matter with B-Wing ?
BRIT : Dr. Spellman .
Our chief vaccinologist .
Within hours of the outbreak , he 'd been sent blood samples
to try and isolate the pathogenic cause .
Unfortunately ...
This is B-Wing now .
God damn it .
How many ?
How many are there ?
There were 80 people working there .
I 've never seen them move like that .
BRIT : They 're dormant .
They 're awaiting stimulus .
Now , this
is vault 139 .
That 's where your samples would be .
This is the skybridge .
That connects B-Wing to the main building here .
And this , is the only thing standing between us and the skybridge .
So ,
what do you propose , Mr. Lane ?
DR. KELLY : You are not serious .
B-Wing 's a maze .
They 'll never make it back alone .
We don 't even know if his theory is correct .
JAVIER : Well , I know I 'm not asking one of you to take him there .
Each has its merits .
Last resort .
It 's too loud .
Let 's go .
Try not to kill one .
It only makes the rest of them more aggressive .
Yeah .
You sure you want to do this ?
Of course I 'm not . Let 's go .
BRIT : Good luck .
See you all shortly .
Good luck .
If anything comes down this hall before we do , you seal these doors for good .
- Understood ? - Okay .
DR. KELLY : There they are .
Go , go .
Hurry up , hurry up , hurry up .
Come on !
They 're fine . They 're fine .
DR. KELLY : Shit .
JAVIER : The vault we need is in 139 .
Go !
Oh , my God .
Left , left , left !
What are you doing ?
She 'll get you to the vault .
That 's the vault .
We can make it .
No , we can 't .
We can 't make it .
Let 's go !
They 're not gonna make it .
You heard what Javi said , we cannot open it .
They 're not alone , we can 't open it !
They are coming back !
We can 't leave them there .
Come on !
Open the door !
BRIT : Run ! DR. RYAN : Run !
Run ! Faster , come on !
Run !
In , in , in !
Come on !
Now where is Gerry ?
Where is he , where is he , where is he ?
Come on , come on , where are you ?
DR. KELLY : 5-6-9-6-4 .
5-6-9-6-4 .
What happened to Gerry ?
Not that one . Not that one .
Oh , shit !
Shit !
BRIT : Jesus .
He 's going to inject himself .
We have no idea which one 's going to work .
We don 't know if any of them will work .
DR. RYAN : If he uses anything he took from that left case ,
he 's dead anyway .
What 's he doing ?
How long does he have to wait ?
Before he 's infected ?
Not long , but ,
that 's not the question we 're really asking , is it ?
- -
Look at them .
He just walked right past him !
He walked right past him !
- - Like it was nobody !
Okay .
GERRY : This isn 't the end .
Not even close .
WOMAN :  Hi , there . This is ...
This is Amy . Is anyone out there ?
INDIAN MAN : Hello . I 'm trying to get in contact with anyone .
AMY : We 've had some luck finding people with this transmission .
GERRY " . We 've lost entire cities .
NEWSWOMAN : When there 's no more people left to infect ,
they go dormant .
Whole cities are lost .
NEWSMAN : The World Health Organization
reports today that help may soon ...
NEWSMAN 2 : ... a hybridized meningitis strain
with components of smallpox and H1N1 .
GERRY : We still don 't know how it started .
NEWSMAN 3 : The World Health Organization has created
a vaccine that works as a kind of camouflage ,
making people who receive it invisible to the infected .
GERRY : We bought ourselves some time .
NEWSWOMAN : Volunteer forces are delivering the vaccine
to areas that have been cordoned off .
MAN : Distribution efforts began in earnest on April 10th ...
NEWSWOMAN : The importance of getting the information
out to those still alive within the quarantine ...
GERRY : But it 's given us a chance .
MILITARY OFFICIAL : If you can get to a colder area ,
to higher ground , they move slower on the ground .
RUSSIAN NEWSMAN : The Battle of Moscow is still raging .
FRENCH NEWSMAN : Initial tests on the so-called camouflage
have been largely successful .
- -
GERRY : Others have found a way to push back .
SQUAD LEADER : Move , move !
All right , juice ' em up !
PILOT : Approaching target .
Permission to engage .
COMMAND OFFICER : Permission granted .
PILOT : All clear .
Light ' em up . Light ' em up .
TELEVANGELIST : It 's permanent !
It 's settled , it 's settled !
It 's over with !
There 's no forgiveness in hell !
Whatever goes to hell , stays in hell !
WOMAN : This is Station 7 in Nebraska ,
broadcasting on the shortwave band .
GERRY : If you can fight , fight .
NEBRASKA WOMAN : Head north if you can .
AMERICAN WOMAN : Hello ?
Is there anyone out there hearing this ?
GERRY : Help each other .
NEWSMAN : Mexico City has been declared a complete loss .
GERRY : Be prepared for anything .
Our war has just begun .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™